This party's going to be killer!!
Harvest of the Dead: Halloween Night is a horror
film directed by Terence Elliott.
It's the day after the events of the first film and Sally Burns and
her friends are preparing for a Halloween party.
As the evening of fun kicks off, unbeknownst to them, The Plague
Doctor and The Creature are preparing to join them.
Sally Burns, played by Dani Thompson.
Dr. Jim Castle, played by David Spinx.
Henry Moore, played by Tim Faraday.
The Plague Doctor, played by Terrence Elliot.
Tia Mucculloch, played by Abby Wareham.
Josh Loocke, played by Olas carter.
Halloween, is a celebration observed in many countries  on 31 October, the
eve of the Western Christian feast of All Hallows' Day.
It is at the beginning of the observance of Allhallowtide, the time in the Christian liturgical year dedicated
to remembering the dead, including saints (hallows), martyrs, and all the faithful departed.
In popular culture, Halloween has become a celebration of horror and
is associated with the macabre and the supernatural.
One theory holds that many Halloween traditions were influenced by Celtic harvest festivals,
particularly the Gaelic festival Samhain, which are believed to have pagan roots.
Some theories go further and suggest that Samhain may have been
Christianized as All Hallows' Day, along with its eve, by the Church.
Other academics say Halloween began independently as a Christian
holiday, being the vigil  of All Hallows' Day.
Celebrated in Ireland and Scotland for centuries, Irish and Scottish immigrants brought many Halloween customs to North America in the 19th
century, and then through American influence various Halloween customs spread to other countries by the late 20th and early 21st century.
Popular activities during Halloween include trick-or-treating (or the related guising and souling), attending Halloween costume parties, carving pumpkins or turnips into jack-o'-lanterns,
lighting bonfires, apple bobbing, divination games, playing pranks, visiting haunted attractions, telling frightening stories, and watching horror or Halloween-themed films.
Some Christians practice the observances of All Hallows' Eve, including attending church services and
lighting candles on the graves of the dead, although it is a secular celebration for others.
Historically, some Christians abstained from meat on All Hallows' Eve, a tradition reflected in the eating
of certain vegetarian foods on this day, including apples, potato pancakes, and soul cakes.
The film explores themes of halloween, halloween party,
serial killer, zombie, occult horror.
The tone is lighthearted and dark.